MICAH MCCLELLAN

959 W 8th Place, Mesa, AZ 85201 | (928)241-1763 | mcclellan.micah.6@gmail.com

Skills Summary

I strive for workplace unity and implement high-performing work ethic. I am a Boy Scout, an honors student, and a volunteer. I am accustomed to versatility, as I have worked in various fields including construction, sales, customer service, food handling, and data entry.

Education

University of Arizona / Current Student

I am attending a 6-month coding bootcamp through this institution. I am becoming proficient in full stack web development practices.

Mesa Community College / Former Student

I have completed the requirements for my General Studies associate degree and am a member of the National Society of Collegiate Scholars. I am currently considering pursuing a degree in Software Engineering.

Holbrook High School / May 2015

I attended Holbrook High School in Holbrook, Arizona, held a 4.0 GPA, was part of the National Honor Society, and graduated with my diploma in the 11th grade.

Experience

Caption Call

Captioning Agent / September 2019 – Present

As a third-party telecommunications employee, I ensure that hard-of-hearing clients receive services that allow them to communicate uninhibited by their hearing loss. Every conversation is strictly confidential and Captioning Agents work around the clock to provide quality calls.

Starbucks

Barista / August 2018 – May 2019

Customer satisfaction is the highest of priorities at Starbucks. Whether they're walking into the store or pulling through our drive-thru, our objective is to put a smile on their face and provide them with exceptional service and quality beverages. Other roles include ensuring that

products are within date-of-use, cleaning responsibilities, and a knowledge of the various instore machines.

Vinx Pest Control

Summer Sales Representative / May 2018 – July 2018

In this role I worked full-time, 6 days a week going door-to-door in various neighborhoods of Dallas suburbs selling pest control.

QK Holdings LLC

Data Entry Clerk / August 2015 – October 2015, January 2018 – April 2018

QK Holdings is the owner of the majority of Denny's locations from California to Oklahoma. In this role I compared bank records to on file records, used the CYMA program on the computer, coded data involving services provided to the company (i.e. various foods, maintenance provided to the facilities, and products used by the company). We ensured that companies who provided services to our Denny's locations were accurately and appropriately paid for their services. In addition, I have experience there doing simple tasks such as check stuffing, copying, filing (both digital and physical copies), and using excel spreadsheets to accurately account for monetary data.

Holbrook Municipal Pool

Lifeguard / July 2015 – September 2015

I spent this summer performing basic lifeguard functions, including providing oversight and protection to swimmers, maintaining the facilities, and accepting payment from swimmers.

Awards and Acknowledgements

Eagle Scout / Boy Scouts of America

Between the ages of 11 and 14, I learned and applied many skills that were taught to me by the Boy Scouts of America (BSA) and verified by an award called a 'Merit Badge.' Some examples of merit badges that I earned include: First Aid, Wilderness Survival, Personal Management, Citizenship in the Nation, Environmental Science, and Communication. Once I was awarded a specified amount of merit badges and also completed a number of community service hours, I was awarded the Eagle Scout award.